>> Brian Holt: 在下面我们会说 npm install -D
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
down here we're gonna say npm install -D
就像那样的漂亮的
eslint eslint-config-prettier like that.
这将为我们安装两种不同的东西。
This is going to install two
different things for us.
很明显的是埃斯皮林特，这是一个代码 linter。
It's gonna obviously eslint,
which is a code linter.
现在我们来谈谈普雷蒂埃和埃林特之间的区别。
Let's talk about what the difference
between prettier and eslint now.
因为人们混淆了两者，这是可以理解的，因此有重叠。
Because people kind of confuse the two and
understandably so, there's overlap.
Prettier 纯粹是担心这里有空间吗 ?
Prettier is purely concerned
with is there a space here?
这里有吗
Is there return here?
这颗文件是怎样的，它是非常机械的，对吧 ?
How does this file star,
it's very mechanical, right?
这很有格式，但是
It's very much, how is this formatted, but
它不关心密码的实际情况，对吧 ?
it doesn't care about what
the code actually does, right?
所以它看起来不存在这个变量吗 ?
So it doesn't look like
does this variable exist?
你知道吗我们是用错误的方法吗
Does this you know,
are we using the wrong method here?
我们是用旧的 JavaScript 吗
Are we using old JavaScript here?
只要它像 prettier 一样不在乎
As long as it parses like
prettier doesn't care.
埃斯特林特更关心风格，对。
Eslint is much more concerned with style,
right.
它跟你用什么方法有关 ?
It's concerned with what
methods are you using?
你知道，交通便利，对吧 ?
You know, accessibility friendly, right?
它可以检查这些东西的种类。
It can check kind of those things.
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
你可以让埃皮林特检查一些机械类的东西。
So you can have eslint check
some of the mechanical stuff.
但它没有那种对那种东西有预力的力量。
But it doesn't have the power that
prettier does for that kind of stuff.
这就是为什么我们要安装漂亮的配置
So that's why we're going to
install the prettier config,
我想说的是 ...
to basically say hey eslint.
那些你有时会担心的事情
That stuff that you sometimes
worry about like spacing,
别担心因为有漂亮的东西对吧
don't worry about it because
prettier has it, right?
所以，安装这两个部件。
So install both of those.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，现在我们都有了。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, and
now we have both of these.
Esrint-config prettier， eslint和
Eslint-config prettier, eslint, and
现在我们要去创建一个 eslint-rc
now we're going to go
create A eslint-rc as well.
所以，制作一个新文件，保存它。
So make a new file, save it.
打电话给这个 .eslint-c.Json
And call this .eslint-c.Json.
>> Brian Holt: 他们要求您将其扩展，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: They require
you give it the extension,
而 .prettierrc 不存在。
whereas .prettierrc does not.
因为您还可以在 YAML 中以及在 JavaScript 中进行配置。
Because you can also configure this in
YAML, as well as in JavaScript as well.
但我们现在要做的是 JSON 方式
But we're gonna do the JSON
way of doing it right now.
>> Brian Holt: 是的，我用了一段时间。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And yes, I use a period.
你有问题吗
Did you have a question?
>> 扬声器 2: 在终端中运行命令时，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: When I ran
the command in the terminal,
它创建了一个名为包装行走的新文件，是 JSON吗 ?
it created a new file called package walk,
is that JSON?
> > Brian Holt: 是，应该这样做。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Yep, it should do that.
好吧让我们先简单谈谈吧
All right, so
let's let's just address that briefly.
如果我回到这里，它就创造了一个新的文件叫做 " 包装锁" 。
If I go back over here, it created
a new file here called package Lock.
所以，包锁是一个锁文件。
So package lock is a lock file.
[ LAUGH] 所以当你将代码部署到生产时
[LAUGH] So what it actually does is
when you deploy your code to production,
实际上它锁定了版本
it's actually locked down the versions.
如果你看看这个你可以看到它有完整性检查
If you look at this you can see
that it has integrity checks, and
比如从哪里下载的，什么版本的，之类的。
like where to download it from and
what version it's on and stuff like that.
你想让它有这个
And you want it to have this,
因为现在我可以在制作过程中安装正确的版本
because now I can install exactly
the correct versions in productions.
所以，我在我的电脑里运行的，正是生产过程中的运行。
So, what I'm running in my computer,
is exactly what's running on production.
你这样做的方式是当你在生产过程中
So, the way that you do that when
you're running in production,
不要在你的本地电脑上做这个但如果我做了晚上我就可以了
don't do this on your local computer,
but if I do it npm, oops, npm ci.
它会用这个包裹锁
It'll actually use the package lock and
要安装正确版本的 JSON 包，对吗 ?
sort of package of JSON to install
exactly the correct version, right?
而如果您执行 NPM 安装，请参阅此处的 JSON 包。
Whereas if you do NPM install see
if I got a package of JSON here.
假设你下周就会释放 1.17.1，对吧 ?
Let's say you know next week
they release 1.17.1, right?
如果我的文件看起来像这样
If my file looks like this.
它实际安装在 1.17.1。
It'll actually install at 1.17.1.
原因在于这是补丁版本，所以
Reason being it's because
that's a patch version, so
应该是兼容的吧
it should be compatible, right?
有道理吗
Does that make sense?
而如果我做 MPMCI ，它会真正安装我所使用的版本。
Whereas if I do MPMCI, it'll actually
install exactly the versions I was using.
因此，它仍将安装 MPM 1.17.0。
So it'll still install MPM 1.17.0.
这能回答你的问题吗
Does that answer your question?
>> 扬声器 2: 是。 谢谢。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah.
Thank you.
> > Brian Holt: Cool.
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Cool.
是的和耶恩日志文件是一样的
Yep, it's the same thing
as a Yarn log file.
据我所知，打包日志和 Yarn 日志完全相同。
The packaged log and Yarn log accomplish,
as far as I know, exactly the same thing.